

# Chris E. Jonak

WEB DEVELOPER
VIDEO/GRAPHIC CREATIVE
BICYCLE MECHANIC
OUTDOOR INDUSTRY PROFESSIONAL
MANAGER

### **CONTACT ME**

Address: Lincoln, NE Phone: 402-326-3535

E-mail: chris@ironbrush.com

Hi! I am a multi-talented professional from Lincoln, NE. I am a versatile asset that has experience and formal education in Videography, Editing, VFX and Photography. I also am currently working toward a career in Web/Software Development. Additionally, I am a Professional Bicycle Mechanic with over 15 years in the Outdoor and Biking Industries!

I have experience in managing both projects and people in a professional setting and love to work as a team. I am most at home working with others to make projects come to life. I am a perfectionist and very loyal when it comes to a company/project that I'm working with/on. Striving to make the best possible product for the client or company is my goal.

I continually work to gain more knowledge and be more profficient every day in both the design and creative world, as well as my other hobbies and interests. I love to work hard and help a company/brand achieve their goals and execute their vision.

My Specialties: Adobe Creative Suite, Canon Cameras, Rhode and Zune Audio Equipment, HTML5, CSS, Javascript, GIT/Github.

Thank You For Your Consideration!



# Chris E. Jonak

WEB DEVELOPER
VIDEO/GRAPHIC CREATIVE
BICYCLE MECHANIC
OUTDOOR INDUSTRY PROFESSIONAL
MANAGER

#### **CONTACT ME**

Address: Lincoln, NE Phone: 402-326-3535

E-mail: chris@ironbrush.com

#### **PROFILE**

Hi! I am a multi-talented professional from Lincoln, NE. I am a versatile asset that has experience and formal education in Videography, Editing, VFX and Photography. I also am currently working toward a career in Web/Software Development. Additionally, I am a Professional Bicycle Mechanic with over 15 years in the Outdoor and Biking Industries!

Check out www.chrisjonak.com for my video reel and contact info!

### **EXPERIENCE**

### SHOP MANAGER - 2012 - 2020

Iron Brush Tattoo

Manager of 17 employees and responsible for scheduling, events, sterile procedures & appointments.

Client Liason & Multimedia/Marketing specialist for the shop.

Videographer/Editor/Photographer - 2005 - Present Freelance work for multiple companies and organizations.
Link to work: www.chrisjonak.com

### Assistant Manager/Media Coordinator/Bicycle Mechanic 2005 - Present

Cycle Works/Moose's Tooth Bicycles & Outdoors
Help manage and educate floor staff, coordinate events for shop
and take care of opening and closing duties. Build & maintain quality
bikes, co-design logos and content for website; shoot & direct video
for shop events.

### **EDUCATION**

Bachelor of Fine Arts - Filmmaking & New Media University of Nebraska-Lincoln - Johnny Carson School of Theatre & Film Lincoln, NE, 2003-2008

### **SKILLS**

Videography

After Effects & Premiere Pro

HTML5, CSS, Javascript, GIT/Github

Bicycle Mechanic

Manager & Project Leader

### **HOBBIES & INTEREST**



















# Chris E. Jonak

WEB DEVELOPER
VIDEO/GRAPHIC CREATIVE
BICYCLE MECHANIC
OUTDOOR INDUSTRY PROFESSIONAL
MANAGER

### CONTACT ME

Address: Lincoln, NE Phone: 402-326-3535

E-mail: chris@ironbrush.com

### References

Anderson Reinkordt
Sr. Software Engineer
TaxJar - a Stripe Company
anderson.reinkordt@gmail.com

Kris Sonderup
Owner
Cycle Works/Moose's Tooth Outdoors
1-(402)-430-4566 - Cell

Tyson Schaffert
Owner
Iron Brush Tattoo
1-(402)-202-9826 - Cell